What keeps you up at night?
This hat. You don't really see it that much anymore,
but sometimes it does happen
And it makes me flabbergasted every time
because it's this kind of knitted hat that people wear
and then they kind of, like,
slouch it
Oh my god, I know exactly
the one
In the back.
I think it's
not dignified to wear it after,
like, age 13
you know what I mean? Like,
I think you need to be locked up
Yeah, these are like grown up people that want to look like elves
Pardon my French
The ones that look like a deflated ball sack
Yeah. Oh,
I know the ones. And shall I tell you what I find about these people?
Their hats are baggier than their trousers
That is something that is wrong
And the pants are so baggy too
The pants are like the kind of harem pants
Oh yeah,
It's either like really tight at the ankle,
like,
Maybe it's cutting off the blood circulation at the ankle
That they think the hat's acceptable
Yeah!
Exactly
Should I tell you what I love about this?
More people need to hate
You need to be told your outfit's shit
I agree
Especially when it comes to fashion
Like, who cares?
We should tell people off
I agree
obviously I'm all for love, kindness,
good feng Shui,
But if you've got a shit hat,
Yeah
You've got a shit hat
Yeah, you should just be thankful
Thank you for telling me
Yeah
So I can take this thing off my head
You're now gonna get DMS being like,
thanks to you, I'll take my hat off
and suddenly I've got a girlfriend
Exactly!
No, this is why I'm saying it
I'm trying to make the world a better place